Anthony S. Moore

I am a Full Stack Engineer, entrepreneur, and former Army Ranger. My various experiences have taught me to think critically and solve problems creatively. I look forward to applying my engineering and leadership skills to impact our society in a meaningful way.

(808) 726-5247 savant@frwdinc.com

EXPERIENCE

Resilient Coders — Full Stack Engineer

January 2018 - Present

- Built a Direct Messaging application using Twitter API
- Built a CRUD application using Node.js and Express
- Built an email collection database
- React development Built an automated savings application
- HTML5, CSS3 front-end design and development.
- Freelance client acquisition

FRWD Inc. — Founder/CEO

December 2016 - Present

Software company that automates savings

- Technical Founder(JavaScript, React, Express. JS, AWS)
 - Mobile and web application that automates savings, credit builder, and investment vehicle.
 - 4K current users
 - Startup Worcester Finalist 2017–2018

Bae :: Before Anyone Else acquired by if/(we) — Brand Ambassador

April 2015 - October 2017

Mobile Dating App

- Successfully launched new app in an experiential marketing environment producing 18K downloads at launch and 350K by the sixth month.
- Assisted in creating social media content to further enhance brand awareness by generating 3 million video views.
- Created and fostered relationships with key stakeholders.

United States Army — First Line Supervisor(Infantry)

November 2007 - January 2014

EDUCATION

Howard University — Bachelor of Arts in History

2016

ACHIEVEMENTS

SF Marathon Finisher, Startup Worcester Finalist '17, Army Ranger, Times Person of The Week '06

SKILLS

JavaScript Node.js MongoDB
JQuery React Express.js Python
Administrative Support
Customer Service Data
Management Leadership
Training Operations
Management Planning and
Scheduling

Volunteer Experience

BUILD Mentor Meet one afternoon a week for 2 hours to help students develop their own business ideas, write business plans, pitch to funders, and launch real businesses. Advise on school-work and college application process.

Code For America Developing a Voice assistant connection to Boston services (Python and AWS). An Alexa skill to answer questions about municipal services in Boston. Currently supports providing an address, asking for trash/recycling pick up days, and snow emergency parking.

Bison Run Founder of a charity run that addresses the homelessness issue in Washington, DC. Donates over \$10K worth of clothes and non perishable food.